Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- Union members seated at wooden tables in suits with white square name tags on their lapels. Turkish writing on reverse. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Furnishings; Gatherings; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A group of four females and one male with some trees in the background. 13.9 x 9.1 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Boys; Gardens; Girls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Trees
- A male in military uniform holding a pipe in his mouth in front of a palm tree. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Military; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Soldiers; Trees; Uniforms
- A male in a dark suit with diamond patterned tie. Turkish writing on the back. Foto Fazil Berki, Ankara, Turkey. 13.2 x 8.4 cm, 5 March 1930 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Ankara, Turkey; Individual Portrait; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young male in military uniform, side profile, looking up and off camera. Turkish writing on the front. 12.8 x 8.4 cm, 3 May 1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Individual Portrait; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Uniforms
- A group of seven young males in military uniforms, outdoors. 8.4 x 13.4 cm, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Countryside; Group Portraits; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Uniforms
- A young couple feeding cake to each other with flowers and a band in the background. Same couple from ref329. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Couple; Eating; Entertainment; Flowers; Music; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints
- A group of six males in military uniform with trees in the background. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Countryside; Gardens; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Trees; Uniforms
- Two older females in dark dress with a young female in the middle dressed as "Snow White" in front of a chalk board. Turkish writing on the back in blue ink. Cengelkoy Ilkokulu (Primary School), Istanbul. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, 26 May 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Education; Girls; Istanbul, Turkey; Performance Play; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkish Writing
- A female in winter clothes, with two young children in front of a stone wall with snow on it. 14.2 x 9.2 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Children; Family; Photographic Prints; Snow
- A group at a wedding, bride is in the center with a older male squatting in front of her with a cigarette in his hand. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Cigarettes; Family; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Veil
- A family group seated at a wedding ceremony on benches with flowers in the foreground and background. Foto Hayri Guven, Istanbul, Turkey. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Brides; Family; Flowers; Grooms; Head Covers; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Wedding Ceremony
- A young male in military uniform, side profile. 13.0 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Individual Portrait; Men; Military; Soldiers; Uniforms
- A seated male in a dark suit with pin stripped pants and a watch on his left wrist. Rasit Ener, Adana, Turkey. Ottoman writing on the back. 13.1 x 8.3 cm, 15 October 1936 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Adana, Turkey; Clocks & Watches; Individual Portrait; Men; Ottoman Writing; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- An older couple standing in front of some curtains, both wearing dark coats. Gorcek, Beyoglu, Istanbul. 13.2 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Coats; Couple; Hats; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Two females standing outside in front of a tree holding winter coats. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Countryside; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
- A group of males of reclining in the sand in front of a mountain, a few men in miltary uniform are standing in the back. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Bathing Suits; Beach; Men; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Uniforms
- A young female in a dark dress with white flower details on the front, with an updo and a tear drop necklace. Armenian writing on the back. 12.5 x 8.5 cm, 17 November 1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Armenian Writing; Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A family group with an older covered woman. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Children; Family; Family Portraits; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young female reclining on a sofa with a plant in the background. Turkish writing on the back, "in our living room". 9.0 x 13.9 cm, 5 June 1941 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Turkish Writing; Women
- Eight young males in front of two windows with the blinds drawn. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Calenders; Furnishings; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A family group, male is in military uniform. Turkish writing on the back. Van, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, 24 October 1941 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Family Portraits; Furnishings; Girls; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Uniforms; Van, Turkey
- Two young females, one female in chevron striped dress with white gloves. Foto Ressam. 8.9 x 6.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  Gloves; Jewelry; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- An older couple holding hands. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Bow Tie; Couple; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Suits
- Two males in suits on a cobbled sidewalk with a painted backdrop. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Furnishings; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- A male in military uniform, with left arm behind his back, standing in a field of flowers in front of a tall tree. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Flowers; Men; Military; Parks; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Trees; Uniforms
- A group of mixed males and females of varying ages, female in the middle is wearing a dark dress with a light feathery collar. Same couple from ref309. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Children; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family; Men; Photographic Prints; Wedding Ceremony; Women
- Two older females in light skirt suits standing in front of some cars in the countryside. 14.1 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Cars; Countryside; Photographic Prints; Suits; Women
- A mixed group of males and females sitting at a wooden table with three ballons in the middle. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Cigarettes; Furnishings; Men; Party; Photographic Prints; Women
- A mixed group of males and females seated and standing around a dinner table with white plates and dark bottles. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, 3 November 1940 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Children; Drinking; Eating; Family; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young couple at their wedding surrounded by flowers, the bride is seated with her veil still covering her face. 12.4 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Couple; Flowers; Photographic Prints; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veil
- A young female holding onto the anchor of boat with swimming. Same female from ref362. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Bathing Suits; Boats; Photographic Prints; Swimming; Women
- A female in a dark dress seated in a chair with a young girl in a dark dress seated on the arm. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Children; Family; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young male in a dark suit, with a mustache, looking down and off camera. 13.5 x 8.2 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
- A female standing with her hand on a wooden chair in front of a painted backdrop, wearing a dark robe on top. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Furnishings; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Robes; Studio Photography; Women
- A woman in a light striped skirt suit on a wooden and rope swing with trees in the backrgound. 13.6 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Suits; Swings; Women
- A family group, two older females, and two young children on a chair. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Children; Family Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A family group in front of a wooden doorway, older veiled female seated, young female standing and older standing female in dark clothes. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Children; Family Portraits; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Women
- A male standing playing the violin, standing female in light dress holding a microphone. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Couple; Entertainment; Men; Microphones; Music; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young couple on their wedding day, groom is in military uniform with a sabre on his belt, female is in a white dress with tiara and veil. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Brides; Grooms; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Swords & Knives; Uniforms; Wedding Veil
- A group of five females and one male of varying ages, youngest female is a a furry patterend coat with checkered boots. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Children; Coats; Family Portraits; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young female looking off camera with a light dress with a dark design on the left chest. Turkish writing on the front. 12.7 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- A woman in a dark dress with stars and hat, leaning against an upright piano. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Hats; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Pianos; Women
- A young girl with a braided crown in her hair, sitting on the arm of a chair with dark boots. 13.9 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- A young male seated completely naked. Studio Atlantis. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Boys; Children; Individual Portrait; Naked; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- Two young males standing inside a grocery store. 13.9 x 9.1 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Coats; Men; Photographic Prints; Shops
- Two males in matching double breasted suits on a deck. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Boats; Bosphorous; Men; Photographic Prints; Uniforms
- A woman helping a toddler in a stripped outfit walk around a table with flowers on it. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Children; Flowers; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young female with an older male both with dark rimmed glasses in front of a table with a birthday cake on it. 13.8 x 9.1 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Eating; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Party; Photographic Prints
- A female in a light patterned dress with a string of pearls on, holding a fork in her left hand. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Eating; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Women
- Three young girls in matching traditional outfits with a young child sitting on wooden chairs. 9.1 x 13.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Children; Furnishings; Girls; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress
- Two men and two women in pajamas and an older female with head cover. 9.1 x14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Gardens; Head Covers; Men; Pajamas; Photographic Prints; Women
- A mixed group sitting on a couch eating and drinking. 9.1 x 12.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Drinking; Eating; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A mixed group standing outside a building with barred windows. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Children; Family; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A family group gathered around a table, with a bold wallpaper print in the background. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- A woman sitting a chair next to a large house plant. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- A young female standing in a black dress, dark purse on a pedestal with a painted backdrop in the background. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Fashion Accessories; Furnishings; Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A female in the woods, in traditional dress with an intricate head-dress. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Countryside; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Traditional Dress; Trees; Women
- An older female with a scarf wrapped around her head and heart shaped buttons on her black outfit. Gorcek, Beyoglu, Istanbul. Same female from ref363. 13.0 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Head Covers; Individual Portrait; Makeup; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young female in a white bathing suit about waist deep in the water. Same female from ref334. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Bathing Suits; Boats; Photographic Prints; Seas; Swimming; Women
- Two females standing in grass. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
- A young female looking off camera in a dark outfit with a braided collar, blush added to her cheeks. Turkish writing on the front. 13.3 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Handtinting; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Women
- An older female looking off camera, dress is dark with floral pattern. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
- A female in a light stripped dress with her hands on her hips in front of a painted backdrop. Studio named embossed. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Makeup; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A female in a dark dress with a light collar and metal chain on her neck, looking off camera. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young child standing in a light knit outfit with a hat and black shoes. Foto Rekor. 13.8 x 8.3 cm, Undated (Bin 1, Folder 24)
  Children; Foto Rekor, Istanbul, Turkey; Hats; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A male in military uniform with a mustache, looking off camera standing in front of some trees. 13.7 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Individual Portrait; Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Trees; Uniforms
- A young girl in a dark off the shoulder dress with a string of pearls. Ottoman writing on the front. Simon's, Paris, France. 11.9 x 9.0 cm, 19 [-?-] 1927 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Ottoman Writing; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A young female in a striped sweater with fake eyelashes drawn on. 12.5 x 8.2 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
- A woman in a skirt suit with a dark bag, standing in front of a house with a cement fence with white rungs. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Streets; Suits; Trees; Women
- A female looking off camera holding on to a chair, wearing a hat, white blouse and dark skirt. 13.7 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Furnishings; Hats; Individual Portrait; Photographic Prints; Women
- A young female in a flower patterned dress with her hand on a chair, standing in a garden. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Furnishings; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Women
- A bride in a chair holding flowers, groom is standing next to her in dark suit with curtains in the background. Turkish writing on the front. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Brides; Grooms; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veil
- Two males standing in a square tiled doorway, male on the left is wearing aviator sunglasses. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Men; Photographic Prints; Shops
- Two older females in a garden with a wooden house in the background with a Siamese cat. 13.8 x 9.1 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Architecture; Cats; Gardens; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Women
- A group of young females and one male in winter coats walking in front of some large stone buildings and trees. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Coats; Men; Photographic Prints; Walking; Women
- A young female in a light dress with big white bow holding flowers in front of a painted backdrop. Studio embossed in bottom left corner. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Girls; Individual Portrait; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A young female walking in the street with a light polka dot dress with bows. 13.5 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Streets; Walking; Women
- Two females standing in the same outfit, holding pens. Studio Nuri. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Banks; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Women
- A young female sitting in a tree in a light colored dress. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Gardens; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
- A group of four males, one squatting, three standing in front of some small trees. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Trees; Uniforms
- An older with her head covered in checked jacket, and two young children. Foto Kartal. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Children; Family Portraits; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A family group, in front of a Christmas tree, two females are wearing straw hats. 13.2 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Christmas Trees; Entertainment; Family; Hats; Party; Photographic Prints
- A young female in a light bathing suit with anchors and life rings on it, sitting on a low stone wall next to the water. 13.8 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Bathing Suits; Boats; Photographic Prints; Seas; Women
- A young female in a patterned dress and satin bow in her hair, holding a childon her lap. Foto S. Sureyya, Istanbul, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Children; Family Portraits; Foto S. Sureyya; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women
- A male in a dark suit holding a baby in a light outfit. N. Baysal, Zonguldak, Turkey. 13.8 x 8.6 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Children; Family Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Zonguldak, Turkey
- Three children in winter coats standing in front of some trees. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Children; Coats; Parks; Photographic Prints; Women
- Two young females standing behind two wooden chairs, female on the left is wearing a dark dress with a light swirled pattern in the middle. 13.5 x 8.1 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
- A woman holding the hand of a baby in overalls with a teddy bear on the floor between them. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Children; Photographic Prints; Toys; Women
- Three older females, one in a flowery bathing suit and hat. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Bathing Suits; Hats; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Swimming Pools
- A bride and groom embracing, with painted backdrop in the background. Turkish writing on the front. 14.5 x 10.0 cm, 21 August 1935 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Brides; Grooms; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkish Writing; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veil
- A group of three females varying ages, young female in a light layered dress with a bouquet of flowers in her hands. 13.4 x 8.3 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Flowers; Girls; Hats; Photographic Prints; Women
- An older female in a checkered dress, holding a young baby while sitting in the grass, donkey in the background. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Children; Countryside; Donkeys; Photographic Prints; Women
- A group of three females standing in front of the Ataturk statue in the Cumhuriyet (Republic) Square, Izmir, Turkey. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Ataturk; Children; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Family; Izmir, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Statues; Women
- An older male in a dark suit and a mustache standing next to some display cases with glasses in them. 13.8 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Photographic Prints; Suits
- Two young females in fancy dress with updos, walking. Turkish writing on the front. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, 9 May 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Girls; Performance Play; Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing
- A young child in a black outfit with black shoes on a wooden pedestal. 13.6 x 8.2 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Children; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography
- A family group, young female is wearing a light dress with white collar and a large bow on her head. 13.5 x 8.7 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Children; Family; Hats; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- A young male in a dark suit leaning on a wall with a cigarette in his mouth with trees in the background. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Cigarettes; Hats; Men; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Suits; Trees
- A bride with veil and drink in her hand, groom has streamers landing on his left shoulder.13.2 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Brides; Grooms; Party; Photographic Prints; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Veil
- A couple dancing in a wood paneled room, female is wearing a dark off the shoulder dress with white lace. 13.6 x 8.4 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Couple; Dancing; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Suits
- A couple standing in dark outfits in front of a body of water with boats and land in the background. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Boats; Coats; Couple; Hats; Photographic Prints; Seas
- A mixed family group of six, bride is in the middle standing with intricate veil and flowers in her hand. 13.3 x 8.5 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Brides; Children; Family Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veil
- An older bride seated on a patterened couch, two older females look on, one with a cigarette in her hand. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Brides; Cigarettes; Fashion Accessories; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Smoking; Wedding Portraits; Women
- A young female standing on an Oriental carpet, in a light dress with buttons up the front. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Furnishings; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Women
- Three young males in dark suits, seated male is looking off camera. 13.7 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Suits
- A group of three females in winter coats with fur lined collars standing in front of a large tree. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Coats; Countryside; Fashion Accessories; Fur Garments; Hats; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
- Two females in skirt suits sitting on a low stone wall with hills in the background. Turkish writing on the front, Zonguldak, Turkey. 13.3 x 8.3 cm, 16 May 1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Photographic Prints; Turkish Writing; Women; Zonguldak, Turkey
- A male in a dark suit with a sailor's hat on standing in front of a body of water and some hills. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Men; Photographic Prints; Seas; Suits
- A bride and groom, groom is standing behind her with his left hand on her elbow. 13.8 x 8.8 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Brides; Grooms; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Wedding Portraits; Wedding Veil
- A young male in military uniform standing in front of some large trees.13.7 x 8.3 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Military; Photographic Prints; Soldiers; Trees; Uniforms
- A couple walking up a winding staircase with square pattern on the rails. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Architecture; Couple; Photographic Prints
- Young males and females inside a house, with a vase of flowers on a table in the foreground. 12.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Children; Furnishings; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- A family group seated on wooden chairs outside in front of a large tree, a dog is laying at the feet of a older lady in a white dress. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Children; Dogs; Family; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Trees